const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אוֹר',
    answers: ['licht', 'gloed', 'glans'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֶרֶץ',
    answers: ['land', 'veld', 'wereld'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'אֲשֶׁר',
    answers: ['die', 'degene', 'hetgene', 'waar'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'בַּיִת',
    answers: ['huis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'בְּרִית',
    answers: ['verbond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'גַּן',
    answers: ['tuin', 'hof'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'דָּבָר',
    answers: ['woord', 'ding'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הַר',
    answers: ['berg', 'bergland', 'gebergte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חַג',
    answers: ['feest'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֶרֶב',
    answers: ['zwaard'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֹשֶׁךְ',
    answers: ['duisternis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'טוֹב',
    answers: ['goed'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'יָם',
    answers: ['zee'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מַיִם',
    answers: ['water'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מֶלֶךְ',
    answers: ['koning'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רוּחַ',
    answers: ['geest', 'wind'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁלוֹם',
    answers: ['vrede', 'gezondheid', 'welzijn', 'welvaart'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שָׁנָה',
    answers: ['jaar'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson4Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson4-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 4 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson4Vocabulary
